script4profit.com 2011-06-02

# EGN Software : Privacy policy | MLM Script | Network Marketing | Reseller | Affiliate | HYIP | Downline Builder | Support System

Kebijakan Privasi

Privacy Policy 

**Introduction**  
Script4Profit.com respects and commits to protect your privacy. Therefore this Private Policy is made in order to make you understand that we respect and keep your Private Information.

Private Information means every information which can be used to identify someone, like name, address, email address or other contact information, whether at work or home. Generally, you can visit our web page without informing us about who you are or revealing any private information about you.. 

This Private Policy organizes how  Script4Profit.com is using and protecting all information form which you give to  Script4Profit.com when you use this site. Script4Profit.com commits to guarantee that your privacy is protected. We ask you to give certain information which you can be identified with it when you use this site, then you can convinced that the data will be used according to this private policy only.

**Collected Information  
** Script4Profit.com collects private information such as name, address, email, phone number, etc... appropriate with the information that our visitors inserted. We need the information to understand your needs and to improve our services quality, like these several reasons:

  * Internal Note.

  * We will use the information to improve products and services.

  * We can send promotion email about new products, special offer as well as other attractive information to your attached email address.

  * Along with the time goes, we may be use the information for the needs of market research. We can contact you by email,p hone, fax or letter. We can use the information to adjust the site with your interest.

**Confidentiality and Security  
** Script4Profit.com will do maximum action according to our policy in order to avoid the lost and misuse of your private information. We keep policy firmly  "No-Spam" which means we are not sell, rent or give email address to third party, without your agreement or permitted by this Private Policy. 

**Uncollected Information  
** When you visit our site, we are not collecting name, email address or other private information, except if you give them to us.  
We do not save credit card data or payment media information which you use in doing the payment of our products, because your payment is process by third party which in this case are merchants like Bank, Credit card processor, etc...

**Purchases**  
If you do purchases from  Script4Profit.com, we need name, address, email, phone number and other private information, but we do not save credit card data or payment media information that you use, because your payment will be processed by third party which in this case are merchants like Bank, Credit card processor, dll...  
  
**Third Party**  
Several pages in  Script4Profit.com may be will include link to third party web site. This site is arranged by their own private proposal, and we are not responsible for their operation. In giving information to third party web site, suggested to you to observe private proposal from those sites before giving your private information.

**Information Distribution**  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies that help us to an investigation or to prevent fraud and deception.  We will only disclose your personal information in state as follows:  
(1) For the purposes or interests of any applicable law, we are required to disclose your personal information,  
(2) In connection with the legal process is or what will take place,  
(3) In order to provide information on authorized institutions with the aim of prevention of irregularities, and reduce credit risk.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please [click here](http://www.script4profit.com/contact)  
  
Changes to this Privacy Policy  
EGN may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

| 

|   
---  
  
-. **egHyip 2.1 has been released**  

**egHyip 2.1** has been released. We add more powerfull features to realize your need. 

For more information about this release, please refer to the [egHyip details here...](http://script4profit.com/eghyip "eghyip")

-. **Change the base currency from USD to IDR**  

We have changed our base currency to our national currency (IDR) , so the US Dollar price will be follow IDR rate. Thank you for your understanding.

-. **Year End Special Offer**  

" **Year End Special Offer** "

  * Reduce **10%** for egbusiness purchases
  * Reduce **20%** for egbusiness additional license purchases

Limited ...

-. **EGN Premium Hosting**  

Please check our hosting plans [here](http://script4profit.com/hosting "EGN Premium Hosting").. All of our hosting packages are optimized to work with our products. Surely a smart choice for those who seriously building a profitable online business.

-. **Indonesian Independence Day Special Price**  

To celebrate " **The 65th of Republic Indonesia Independence Day** "on 17th August 2010, EGN gives **Special Price of 10% - 40% discount** for every purchase. This special price only valid from  [other news...](http://www.script4profit.com/news)
